Did you know
that up to 300 serial killers
are active on any given day?
I like to think
of them as my friends.
Serial killer Joe Carroll's life
came to an end
early this morning.
Is it true?
Resurrection!
Joe Carroll lives.
Aah!
This new cult...
Drive, dear.
Yes, mother.
They will kill you.
Probably.
You have
a family--me.
If something happened
to you, that would end me.
Joe faked his death,
started again.
How does Lily Gray
fit into all this?
She's the female version of Joe.
You take from me,
I take from you.
That's my dad's house.
Mike!
Don't do this.
They're all gonna pay.
You've become the man you hate.
Do it!
Arrest him.
After all this is over,
you and me, we're
gonna go have a life.
Kiss her!
Yeah!
Gina looks so beautiful.
I mean, I usually hate
weddings, but this one is--
No. It's special.
Yeah. Uh-oh.
Two o'clock.
There's a hottie by the bar,
and she's checking you out.
No. Come on.
Yes.
- Really?
- Definitely.
Here goes nothing.
Mm-hmm.
So friend of the bride
or friend of the other bride?
How long did you
work on that line?
Not good enough?
It was a little
underwhelming, to be honest.
Wow! This is not
at all
how I expected this this to go.
You want to try again?
How about this?
Better?
Yeah. That works.
Wow! You're beautiful.
- Mmm. Ryan.
- What?
I love this song.
No. Uh-huh. No.
I don't dance.
- Yes, you do.
- Gwen, I don't.
You've been holding out on me.
- I don't.
- I know it.
♪ A man on the scene ♪
♪ I can give you what you want ♪
♪ if you come go home with me ♪
♪ I got some good old lovin' ♪
♪ and I got more in store ♪
♪ when I get through
throwing it on you ♪
♪ you got to come back
for more ♪
♪ boys will come
a dime by the dozen ♪
♪ that ain't nothing
but 10-cent loving ♪
♪ pretty little thing,
let me light your candle ♪
♪ 'cause, mama, I'm sure
hard to handle now ♪
♪ you know, hey ♪
♪ yeah ♪
♪ They are lonely ♪
♪ lonely and feeling blue ♪
♪ these arms of mine... ♪
Hey come here.
Mike!
- Hey.
I didn't know if
you were gonna make it.
I almost didn't I came
right from the airport.
Ah. This is Gwen.
Mike, Gwen.
He talks about you all the time.
Ok. Hi.
You're responsible
for the big grin
on this guy's face.
Mike.
You look great.
Thanks. Uh, this is--
this is Tom Reyes.
Mike Weston.
You're just back from the field?
Yeah.
Uh, Tom works for our
hostage rescue team
in New York.
"Our." So it's true.
You joined the bureau.
I've got about
a month on the job.
Heh.
You look thirsty.
Do you want a drink?
- Yeah, yeah. Let's go.
- Come on.
Lead the way.
♪ Up and down the highway ♪
- Hey.
- Ooh. Careful.
Oh, yeah. That was
definitely my fault.
Look at her.
She's been through hell.
She deserves a little joy, huh?
Yeah. I think we all
deserve some peace.
Amen to that. I know I'll
feel a whole lot better
when they finally put Joe
Carroll out of his misery.
Less than a month, man.
Well, here's to all the
questions and second guessing
dying along with him.
Salud.
It would appear that
the FBI allowed Mr. Hardy
to conduct his own
lawless reign of terror
to find Joe Carroll.
That couldn't be further
from the truth, congressman.
You have anything you'd
like add, Agent Hardy?
Nope.
Well, while we're appreciative
of the work you've done
in apprehending Joe Carroll,
I don't think we can
in good conscience
simply ignore your methods
and the many lives lost.
That said, at this time,
our investigation has found
no substantive evidence
of criminal wrongdoing.
Hello.
Sorry I can't stay late.
I have the early shift
in the ER tomorrow.
Stay at my place.
It's close to the hospital.
Again?
Yeah. Why not?
So you're saying you
like having me around?
Uh, yeah. I think
you know that.
Because my lease is up
at the end of the month.
Oh! I see what
you did there.
You said we'd talk about it.
And we will,
but right now, cake!
Must have cake.
Ryan, you coward.
Oh. I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to frighten you.
Yeah. It's ok.
Was that Ryan Hardy
you were talking to?
Yeah. Do you know him?
Just from the news.
I should really get back inside.
He's the guy who caught
Joe Carroll, right?
Yeah, that's right.
People are calling him a hero.
The toasts are starting.
Excuse me.
Make a toast.
Go ahead, Ryan.
Whenever you're ready.
Just fire away.
When you meet the right girl,
you just know.
And may--maybe
you're not even looking,
and then suddenly, there she is,
and she's such a perfect fit,
you can't deny it,
and you got to--
you got to give her
a place in your heart,
a place that you
didn't even think
existed anymore,
and then everything changes,
and where there was hurt,
there's comfort.
Where there was dark,
there's light.
If you find that kind of love,
you got to hang on, man.
Amen to that.
You don't let go.
Cheers.
Liar!
You killed my daughter!
She was at the Korban compound!
You shot her in cold blood!
She did not deserve that!
She was 19.
Sir.
Sherry--Sherry was
such a beautiful girl.
She just lost her way.
You're a murderer.
You and Joe Carroll
should be sharing a cell
on death row.
Guys.
Let him go.
Are you sure?
It's all right.
Let him go.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Morning.
Hey.
Sleep ok?
Yeah. You?
Your FBI buddies sure know how
to throw a wedding.
I got to say I didn't
see that coming.
Yeah.
Ryan, that man's grief
was heartbreaking,
but you can't blame yourself
for his daughter's death.
You were doing your job.
I know.
How many more people would
Joe Carroll have killed
if you hadn't stopped him?
But so many lost
their lives, you know,
and it's easy to see them as
just an extension of Joe,
but I don't even
recognize that name--Sherry.
The more I really
think about it,
there's only a handful
of names that I do remember.
Joe Carroll turned those
people into killers.
But their lives, their
families should still matter.
And they do.
Then why don't I
remember their names?
Hopkins, track down a
file for me, will you?
Deceased Korban member named
Sherry, last name unknown.
I'll see what I can find.
All right. Thanks.
Mendez.
Hey.
How's Dawn holding up?
Wasn't how we dreamed our
wedding reception would end,
but she's hanging in there.
Oh. Make it up to her
on your honeymoon?
Which I had to postpone till
after Joe Carroll's execution.
So she's just loving being
married to the FBI.
Pretty much.
For the past 9 months,
I've been following up
on rumors of Mark Gray sightings
in Europe and South America.
I do believe I've
isolated and frozen most
of the considerable
Gray fortune.
I feel confident that
following through
with this protocol will eventually
force Gray into the open.
Thank you, Agent Weston.
Carroll's execution's set
for the end of this month.
We all need to be on the lookout
for any suspicious activity.
We believe we've eliminated
his network of followers,
but as you all know, we could
never be absolutely sure.
Carroll himself is not a threat.
Since his recapture, he's been
under 24-hour
lockdown
in an undisclosed
federal facility.
I've been monitoring the web.
There's a lot of chatter but no
confirmed threats to public safety.
Stay on that.
I need you all to be vigilant.
A new threat could expose
itself at any moment.
Her.
Hi.
Hey.
I'm Natalie,
and, uh, that's
my husband Kenny.
It's our second
wedding anniversary.
Congratulations.
The first year's the hardest.
Tell me about it.
Anyway, my husband
thinks you're stunning.
That's sweet.
So would it be wrong if I asked
if you were working?
I'd be happy to make
your anniversary
something to remember
just so long as you know couples
cost a little bit more.
Hold on, hold on.
Hold on, Kenny.
This has to be fun
for both of you.
No, no, no.
Stay where you are.
Enjoy the anticipation.
Make it nice and tight.
What the hell was that?
Kenny, I-I think
it's coming from the closet.
No, no, no!
Unh!
You started without me, Daisy?
Don't pout, Kyle.
I was just getting
my engine started.
You know the best
is yet to come.
They were on their
second wedding anniversary.
Oh, sweet.
What do I call you?
Natalie.
And what's my name?
Kenny,
and you're kind of aggro.
It's good to have
you back, Mike.
Doesn't seem like I've
been missed around here.
Well, you have.
I've missed you.
Thanks.
Hey. Gwen--
she seems great.
How long have you two
been together?
About 6 months. Honestly,
I haven't felt like this
in a really long time.
And Joe?
You been to see him?
Nope. I've moved on.
You will, too,
as soon as we catch Mark.
Who knows? Maybe
you'll take my job.
What, are you leaving us?
When it's time.
Don't go.
I have to go.
No, you don't.
We've talked about this.
Mark is still out there.
And every law enforcement
agency in the world
is hunting him.
That doesn't matter.
Catching him is my job.
You mean killing him.
If that's what it takes.
Like Lily.
I know I put you
in a bad position.
A bad position?
Mike, I covered up an execution.
They murdered my father
in front of me.
I have no problem putting
her down the way I did.
If you do, I'm sorry.
Mike, please.
Stay here with me.
I can't.
Look. I'll call you
when I land.
Don't.
We should catch up sometime.
Yeah. When things
calm down around here.
Agent Hardy.
Sherry, last name Miller.
19 years old from Queens.
She died of a through-and-through
gunshot wound
to the neck during
the raid on Korban.
No way to know who shot her.
Thanks.
What are you doing, Ryan?
Guy from the wedding.
It's his daughter.
She was one of Joe Carroll's
followers, right?
Yeah.
We put all of that
stuff behind us.
Just let it go.
Yeah.
I'm Ryan Hardy.
Yeah, I know who you are.
Sorry to bother you.
I was hoping I could
talk to you about your daughter.
I just needed to say I'm sorry
about what happened to Sherry.
No parent should have to
bury a child.
I loved my daughter,
but she was a troubled girl.
I don't blame you
for what happened.
Is your husband here? I was
hoping I could talk to him, too.
Jimmy.
Can I help you?
You're Sherry's father?
Yes.
You were supposed to be
here 20 minutes ago.
Knowing you two,
I know what was going on
in here 20 minutes ago.
I'd say right on time.
This is all wrong.
We have to make this perfect,
or he'll kill us all.
Looks like
the crazy is starting.
No!
Unh!
They were killed this afternoon.
Liar!
Ryan.
They've told lies!
Ryan?
Why don't
I remember their names?
Ryan.
Get an I.D.
on our victims?
Kenny and Natalie Brooks,
in town from Greenwich.
Bartender says he saw them talking
to a prostitute at the bar,
but all he remembers
is that she was a brunette.
You think this was Joe's people?
Uh, there's no mention
of Joe here, just me.
This is the second time
in 24 hours
that I've been called a liar.
Yeah. We'll, that can't
be a coincidence.
Our fake dad from the wedding's
got to be tied to us somehow.
Wedding photographer's
already pulling photographs.
Hopefully we'll get
a match in the system.
Hotel has the room listed
as empty,
so we think that our hooker used
a maid's card key to get in.
Oh. The maid's body
is in the closet.
Hotel security video?
Disabled during the attack.
Our girl knew what
she was doing.
She wasn't alone.
Definitely more than
one attacker.
Most likely a male
based on the strength
required to stage this,
and they're not done.
How do you know?
They got some kind
of an agenda or message,
and they know that they
haven't given us enough yet
to figure it out.
Which means the killing
is only beginning.
You two have a room, you know?
Our love cannot be
contained in a room.
Hey. Andrew,
sweetie,
do you have any more
of those yogurts?
You mean my yogurts.
Listen. I've clearly marked
my food in the fridge,
so if you two could
just respect the labels.
Heh heh.
Are you kidding?
Not even a little bit.
This little forced marriage
between us
is going to work much better
if we have boundaries.
Whatever, bro.
Has he even come downstairs?
Did he ask how it went?
No. He's in one
of his moods.
Well, we have a job
to do, all right?
Let's just get it done,
and we can get our lives back.
Ok.
We're still adjusting
to the time difference.
There is no time difference
between here and Ohio.
Just give me a minute.
I'll rally.
You know what?
Forget it.
I'll do this one myself.
We'll meet you later.
Maybe I should go with him?
He's fine.
That guy is one seriously
twisted individual.
She was, uh...
she was so beautiful.
I can't believe that
she's really gone.
I can't believe I'll
never get to hold her again
or...
I miss my little girl so much.
Your daughter sounds like
she was really special.
I lost my sister
a few weeks ago.
Oh. I'm so sorry.
Look. Uh, how about
I buy you a cup of coffee
and we can talk about it?
I got to say this guy's
pain felt so real.
It's hard to believe
he was faking it.
My guess is he
probably gets some kind
of perverse pleasure from it,
grew up unable to access
any kind of real emotion,
so he started mimicking it,
found out he had a true talent.
Now he's Laurence Olivier.
Ryan, security called.
Gwen's downstairs.
Ok. Be right back.
Yeah.
Hey.
Figured you could use
a decent cup of coffee.
Wow.
I got cake pops, too.
Oh, wow. Thanks.
You're really sweet.
This is really not
a good day for this.
Sure. I understand.
Are you--you ok?
Yeah, just busy.
Honestly, it looks
like it's gonna be
very busy for a while,
so there's a pretty good chance
that you're not gonna see
that much of me if at all.
What are you doing?
What? What do
you mean?
If feels like you're
pushing me away.
No, I'm not.
It's happening again, isn't it?
Is it Joe?
No. I--I--I, uh, I think
it's something else,
but there is a real possibility
that it's gonna take over
my life for a while,
and I just--
I want to protect
you from this stuff.
We've got something
really special, Ryan.
I know you feel it, too.
Don't be so quick
to throw us away.
Ryan, we got a hit
on our grieving father.
Andrew Jacobs.
His driver's license
was issued 10 months ago.
Before that, he didn't exist.
Address in Greenpoint.
It's ok. Go.
I'll call you.
Thanks for the coffee.
Warm and inviting it's not.
Don't tell me
you got soft overseas.
Not a chance.
Wait, wait.
_
First, you're the liar, now me.
Why does this feel so familiar?
Because it is.
You lived this moment,
you both did.
It's a tableau
of Max shooting Luke.
You're right.
I was standing in the doorway.
Mike, you were
on the ground there.
Luke was about to kill you,
and I fired.
Mark is behind this.
♪ They say forget about him ♪
♪ you're better off
without him ♪
I used goat cheese this time.
Saw it on "Martha."
Supposed to really
elevate the dish.
♪ Guy-yyy ♪
♪ but I love him so ♪
♪ I can't forget... ♪
Just be honest with me, ok?
I can take it.
♪ No, no ♪
♪ it's easier to cry ♪
♪ easier to cry ♪
♪ ahh, ahh ♪
Well?
Hmm.
♪ Can't forget him ♪
♪ no, no ♪
It's delish, little bro.
Martha's got nothing on you.
♪ Cry ♪
♪ easier to cry ♪
Thanks.
Well, there's plenty
more, so eat up.
Ok, ok, everybody.
Listen up.
Our boy Mark is punishing us
for killing
his family last year.
These murder scenes
are re-creations
of their deaths.
That's Max there with the gun
when she killed Luke,
Agent Weston on his knees,
and that's me
right after I killed Giselle,
Mark's adopted sister.
The scenes that Luke
and Mark staged last year
were more rudimentary.
They used whatever was at
hand to pose the bodies.
This is much more sophisticated.
Which means that Mark
has his own followers now.
Mark.
We're getting ready
to go do the next one.
You said you wanted to come.
I can't.
You sure?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Go ahead without me.
Ok.
No problem.
What do you mean can't?
Hey. This is
our revenge!
You have to go!
You don't understand.
It's too painful.
Painful? Try being shot
in the friggin' head!
I know. You're right. I'm sorry.
Well, don't
be sorry, little bro.
Be angry.
Yeah.
They killed us,
and they covered it up.
We've got to make them pay.
We have alerts out on
Mark across the city.
Why is he writing you've
lied at every scene?
- Lied about what?
- I don't know.
Ryan, I'm not buying--
He's delusional, Gina.
Him and his brother
were psychotically close.
I can't imagine what
losing Luke has done
to his fractured mind.
But I do know who his next
target's gonna look like--
Lily Gray.
I don't get it. Why
would he sit this one out?
I'd unleash hell
on earth if you got killed.
I guess Mark's just a little
more sensitive than you.
Why am I letting
you guys have all the fun?
Come on. Let's go
kill some people.
Max, got anything?
Pull it up.
CCTV camera
at the Lincoln
Center subway stop
took this 20 minutes ago.
Ok. He's not dressed
like that for fun.
Any catered events
in the neighborhood?
I mean, it's New York.
There's probably 50.
We got to think like Mark.
He's looking for a
doppelganger for his mother.
Where would he go to find her?
Got it. Art fundraiser
5 blocks from there.
That's it!
Have NYPD meet us there.
Code two, urgent!
Luke, what about her?
Hmm. Mom was way prettier.
Yeah. You're right.
Hi!
Oh, she's perfect.
We're on.
Excuse me.
Oh! Oh!
I'm so sorry.
It's ok.
Um, I-I just need
a bathroom.
There's a big line
for the one up here,
but the one downstairs is empty.
Here. Let me
show you.
You think Mark's gonna be here?
It's his mother.
He won't leave
this tableau to his followers.
Ok. Fan out.
FBI! Don't panic!
Aah!
Ugh! Agh!
You ok?
I'm good.
Where's Mark?!
Sorry. You're too late.
Let me out!
Let me out, let me out!
Let me out of here!
Why you just sitting there?
Come on.
Get out of the car.
Come on!
Let me out!
I don't think
I can do this, Luke.
Well, you have to.
You have to kill her
and finish what we started.
Hey. Will you shut up!
Nobody's talking to you.
Will you come with me?
Of course.
I'm always with you.
Yeah.
Yeah. I know.
Please!
Don't do this.
No!
Mom! Mom, I'm sorry.
No. Get up.
No, no, no. No.
Hey. Don't go.
Don't go. Don't go.
Please don't go.
Don't leave me.
Please don't leave me.
I've been so lonely without you.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Please don't leave me.
Come back.
Knock it off.
Eh, you're no fun.
When's the last time
you had a good cry?
It can be incredibly cathartic.
Yeah, but it's gonna make you
all the wrong kinds
of friends in prison.
You know, you should
have seen your face
when I called you a murderer.
I mean, you were shocked,
but there was a part of you
that welcomed it
because you know it's true.
Where's Mark Gray?
Oh. Such
a sad story.
His whole family was killed
by you and your friends.
Yeah. What do you
care, huh?
What's Mark to you?
Thank you for coming.
I didn't know who else to call.
I'm a sucker
for a good revenge tale,
but this--
heh heh heh--
this is gonna be so much more.
You have no idea what's coming.
Ok. So this moment
may be new to you,
but I've sat in this chair,
and I've had this
very conversation,
and the guy I had it
with is on death row,
and I'm still here.
So you can spare me
the scary proclamations.
Do you have the time?
Got someplace you got to be?
No, but...
you do.
♪ Go your way ♪
♪ I'll take the long way round ♪
♪ oh, I'll find
my own way down ♪
♪ oh, as I should ♪
♪ hold your gates ♪
♪ as croak in the midas touch ♪
♪ a joke in the way
that we rust... ♪
Hey. Stop it.
We have to go home, ok?
The FBI got Andrew. How
long before they get us?
Calm down, Daisy.
If we leave here
before we finish,
what do you think's
gonna happen?
Everything we have will be gone.
We'll spend the rest of our
short lives on the run.
He'll make sure of it.
Mark has no idea
what's really going on.
And we need to make sure
it stays that way.
♪ And you'll find loss ♪
♪ and you'll fear
what you found ♪
♪ when weather comes,
tear him down ♪
♪ there will be
oats in the water ♪
♪ there will be birds
on the ground ♪
♪ there will be things
you never asked her ♪
♪ oh, they tear at you now ♪
♪ and hold your gates ♪
♪ as croak in the midas touch ♪
♪ a joke in the way
that we rust ♪
♪ and breathe again ♪
♪ And you'll find loss ♪
♪ and you'll fear
what you found ♪
♪ when weather comes,
tear him down ♪
♪ there will be
oats in the water ♪
I'm so glad you called me.
Me, too.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have
pressured you earlier.
No. You were right.
I was pushing you away.
It's my pattern,
and, uh, I don't want
to do it anymore.
I need you.
I need you, too.
Today was hard.
You really helped me
get through it.
You did great.
I'm proud of you.
Thanks.
Tomorrow will be easier.
Are you kidding me?
Tomorrow will be awesome
because tomorrow
one of them dies.
Hmm.
Heh.